第一章，美式发音。把声音放低，把声音送出去。我们从
Chapter One. The American Sound. Deepen your voice. Project it out. Let's start at
最开始讲起。就像哲学家说的：从你自己开始，并先定义术语。
the beginning. As the philosophers say, start with yourself and define your terms.
你的口腔由哪些部分组成？它们如何配合？什么是辅音？什么是
What are the parts of your mouth? How do they interact? What's a consonant? What's
元音？我们从最基本的声音开始，来参观一下口腔。
a vowel? Let's take a tour of the mouth, starting with the most basic sound.
练习 1-1：起点。mmm。我们从 mmm 这个音开始。它非常
Exercise 1-1. The starting point. Mmm. Let's start with the mmm sound. It's super
容易发。你只要把双唇合上，然后哼出声。这里你会注意到几件
easy to do. All you do is put your lips together and hum. You'll notice a couple
事情：你的双唇相触，气流从鼻腔出来，
of things here. Your lips are touching, the air is coming out through your nose,
并且是连续流出的。把手放在喉咙上，说 mmm，观察一下
in a continuous stream. Put your hand on your throat and say mmm and observe that
你能在指尖感到振动。这说明 M 音是
you can feel a vibration in your fingertips. This means that the M sound is
发声的，而不是气声，mmm。这个练习告诉你关于辅音 M 的四个要点：
spoken and not whispered, mmm. This exercise tells you four important things
一，接触点：双唇。二，气流从口腔哪里出来：鼻腔。
about the consonant M. One, point of contact, lips. Two, where the air comes
三，气流如何出来：滑音。四，这个音是发声还是气声：
out of your mouth, nose. Three, how the air comes out, glide. Four, if the sound
发声。
is spoken or whispered, spoken.